Guide to the Stanton family papers, 1782-1979
Stanton family papers, 1782-1979
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Stanton family papers, 1782-1979.
3930
Stanton family.
.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, clippings, account book, deeds, survey and indenture papers, booklets, hymnal, New Testament, calendar.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes letters, clippings, account books, and other papers of the Walter Stanton family.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes letters, clippings, account books, and other papers of the Walter Stanton family. Also, reminiscences of Walter Stanton. Named in the papers are Thomas Older, Christopher Burlingham, John Cochran, Gertruyd Cochran, the Gaston family, and the Levy family.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Stanton family.; Burlingham, Christopher.; Cochran, Gertruyd.; Cochran, John.; Gaston family.; Levy family.; Older, Thomas.; Stanton, Walter.
Form and Genre Terms:
Reminiscences.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence and Papers
  - Quit claim deed, Thomas Older to Christopher Burlingham, 1782 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Copy of survey and indenture between John Cochran and wife Gertruyd, and Christopher Burlingham, Saratoga, Albany County, NY, 1783, 1758 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Printed Epistle from yearly meeting to ..., Meetings of Friends..., William Alexander, Clerk, London., 1800 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sevy family letters, 1835, 1852-1854 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letters and papers, Gaston and others, 1872, 1876, 1881-1887, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advertisement calendar: Thomas Elliott, Cigar Box Factory, Ithaca, NY, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reminiscences of Walter Stanton (photocopy), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Printed Items
  - Bartholomew golden wedding commemorative booklet, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church directory, Freeville and West Dryden, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Freeville High School, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 100th anniversary of the United Methodist Church, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 125th anniversary of the United Methodist Church, Freeville, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Account book with pasted-in clippings and loose items, 1869-1872 (Box 1)
  - Copy of Jack, the Bear Man by J.R. Musick, the Nickel Library, New York. Second edition, Series 12, No. 331., July 7, 1883 (Box 1)
  - Hymn Book for Reformed Methodist Connexion in U.S. and Canada belonging to John Pease, 1833 (Box 1)
  - The Polyglott New Testament with Marginal Readings New York, published by J.C. Riker, 1831. Belonging to Maria Stackett. Clippings pasted in., 1846 (1831) (Box 1)